A generation began in his backyard.
Taking Woodstock is a music, comedy, drama film directed by Ang Lee.
The story of Elliot Tiber and his family, who inadvertently played a pivotal role in making
the famed Woodstock Music and Arts Festival into the happening that it was.
When Elliot hears that a neighboring town has pulled the permit on a hippie music festival, he calls the
producers thinking he could drum up some much-needed business for his parents' run-down motel.
Three weeks later, half a million people are on their way to his neighbor’s farm in White Lake, New York, and Elliot finds
himself swept up in a generation-defining experience that would change his life–and American culture–forever.
Elliot Teichberg, played by Demetri Martin.
Sonia Teichberg, played by Imelda Staunton.
Jake Teichberg, played by Henry Goodman.
Michael Lang, played by Jonathan Groff.
Max Yasgur, played by Eugene Levy.
Billy, played by Emile Hirsch.
Taking Woodstock is a 2009 American historical musical comedy-drama film
about the Woodstock Festival of 1969, directed by Ang Lee.
The screenplay by James Schamus is based on the memoir Taking Woodstock: A True
Story of a Riot, a Concert and a Life by Elliot Tiber and Tom Monte.
The film premiered at the 2009 Cannes Film Festival, and opened in New York and Los
Angeles on August 26, 2009, before its wide theatrical release two days later.
It received mixed reviews and was a box office failure.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, biography,
woodstock, new york, music festival, dog tag.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.